Rehn Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Photographs, 1871-1966, undated, Series 6:; (Boxes 22, 24, and OV 25; 1.0 linear feet; Reel 5872)
  - Works of Art, circa 1905, 1960-1964, undated, 6.2:
    - Gatch, Elsie Driggs (See Driggs, Elsie) (Box 22, Reel 5872)
    - Giles, Howard, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1036)
    - Griffin, Walter, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1038)
    - Gross, Sidney, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1040-1049)
    - Harshe, Robert B., undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1051-1064)
    - Hartman, Rosella, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1066-1069)
    - Hassam, Childe, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1071)
    - Henri, Robert, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1073-1113)
    - Hopper, Edward, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1115-1133)
    - Hubbard, Earl Wade, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1135-1136)
    - Johnson, Eastman, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1138-1141)
    - Kaufman, Irving, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1143-1152)
    - Kimball, Yeffe, undated (Box 22, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - King, Gwyneth, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1155-1156)
    - Kozlow, Richard, undated (Box 22, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Lawson, Ernest, undated (Box 22, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Lie, Jonas, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1160-1161)
    - Luks, George, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1163-1165)
    - MacIver, Ian T., undated (Box 22, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Martin, Homer D., undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1175)
    - Marsh, Reginald, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1168-1173)
    - Mattson, Henry, undated (Box 22, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - McFee, Henry Lee, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1178-1185)
    - Melchers, Gari, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1187)
    - Murphy, J. Francis, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1189-1190)
    - Picken, George, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1192-1193)
    - Poor, Henry Varnum, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1195-1196)
    - Rehn, F.K.M., [Sr.], (Oversized item housed in Box 24) (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1198)
    - Rosen, Charles, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1203-1204)
    - Russo, Alexander, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1206)
    - Schweider, Arthur, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1208-1209)
    - Slatin, Yeffe Kimball (See Kimball, Yeffe) (Box 22, Reel 5872)
    - Soyer, Raphael, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1211)
    - Speicher, Eugene, undated, (2 folders) (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1213-1293)
    - Strater, Henry, 1960-1964 (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1295-1300)
    - Templeton, Robert, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1302-1307)
    - Thayer, Abbott H., undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1309)
    - Trebilcock, Paul, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1311-1329)
    - Tucker, Allen, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1331-1340)
    - Tucker, Richard Derby, 1963 (Box 22, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Twachtman, John H., undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1343-1344)
    - Watkins, Franklin C., undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1346-1347)
    - Wilder, Ruth, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1353-1356)
    - Weir, J. Alden, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1349-1351)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1358-1378)
  - Reginald Marsh's Photographs, 1871-1952, undated, 6.3:
    - Reginald Marsh, 1900-1947, undated, (Oversized items housed in Box 24 and OV 25) (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1381-1427)
    - Family Album, 1912-1915 (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1431-1473)
    - Family and Friends, 1871-1952, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1475-1496)
    - Meyer, Herbert [?], undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1498-1507)
    - Childhood Drawings, 1902-1906, undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1509-1516)
    - Buildings (mother's church, father's church, and unidentified), undated (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1518-1522)
    - Oversized Photos, Reginald Marsh, 1900-1947, undated, (Oversized items scanned with Reel 5872, frames 1381-1427) (Box 24 (sol), Reel 5872)
    - Oversized Photos, Reginald Marsh, 1900-1947, undated, (Oversized items scanned with Reel 5872, frames 1381-1427) (Box OV 25, Reel 5872)
  - Miscellaneous Subjects, circa 1923, 1928, 1950, undated, 6.4:
    The Carnegie International Exhibition photograph includes Ernest Lawson, Homer Saint-Gaudens, Colin Gill, Anto Carte, Jonas Lie, Robert Spencer, Mahonri Young, Rockwell Kent, and Guillaume Lerolle.
    - Dog, undated (Box 22, Reel unmicrofilmed)
    - Exhibitions, circa 1923 and 1950 (Box 22, Reel 5872, Frame 1526-1529)
    - Carnegie International Exhibition, Jury of Award and American Committee of Selection, 1928, (Oversized item scanned with Reel 5872, frame 981) (Box 24 (sol), Reel 5872)
    - Rehn, F.K.M. [Sr.], undated, (2 copies; autographed by 30 artists; oversized item scanned with Reel 5872, frame 1198) (Box 24 (sol), Reel 5872)